{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Luke Skywalker's home planet?",
      "alternatives": ["Tatooine", "Naboo", "Alderaan", "Hoth"],
      "answer": "Tatooine"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Luke's father?",
      "alternatives": ["Obi-Wan", "Yoda", "Anakin", "Han Solo"],
      "answer": "Anakin"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
      "alternatives": [
        "X-Wing",
        "Millennium Falcon",
        "TIE Fighter",
        "Star Destroyer"
      ],
      "answer": "Millennium Falcon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who trained Anakin Skywalker?",
      "alternatives": ["Yoda", "Mace Windu", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Qui-Gon Jinn"],
      "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the main villain in the original trilogy?",
      "alternatives": ["Darth Maul", "Darth Vader", "Kylo Ren", "Palpatine"],
      "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Luke Skywalker's mentor?",
      "alternatives": [
        "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
        "Leia Organa",
        "Han Solo",
        "Chewbacca"
      ],
      "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the planet where Yoda goes into exile?",
      "alternatives": ["Dagobah", "Endor", "Mustafar", "Kamino"],
      "answer": "Dagobah"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who killed Emperor Palpatine?",
      "alternatives": ["Luke Skywalker", "Darth Vader", "Rey", "Mace Windu"],
      "answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Jedi order that protects the galaxy?",
      "alternatives": [
        "Sith Order",
        "Jedi Order",
        "Galactic Order",
        "Order of the Force"
      ],
      "answer": "Jedi Order"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the creator of Star Wars?",
      "alternatives": [
        "Steven Spielberg",
        "George Lucas",
        "J.J. Abrams",
        "James Cameron"
      ],
      "answer": "George Lucas"
    }
  ]
}
